IT'S LIKE WASHING HIS
DREAMS. IT'S A DREAM
HE DIDN'T REALLY GET
TO HAVE. ALL RIGHT.
WITH HIS SURGERY, HE
CAN'T PLAY CONTACT SPORTS.
IT'S MOTIVATION TO NOT
LET WHAT HE WENT
THROUGH HOLD HIM DOWN.
OH, WOW.
KING JEREMIAH, MAN.
YOU GOT SOME ICE
IN YOUR HAIR.
THAT LOOKS AWESOME.
UNFORTUNATELY, THESE KIDS HAVE
ALL HAD THEIR CHILDHOODS
TAKEN AWAY FROM THEM.
SO I ARRANGED FOR
THEIR FAVORITE YOUTUBERS TO
JOIN AND ALL PLAY
TOGETHER. WHAT'S GOING ON?
HAVE YOU SEEN LAURENCE?
YES. WHAT IF I
TOLD YOU SHE'S BEHIND
YOU?
WE SURPRISED TWO KIDS
WITH KSI. MAYBE TURN
AROUND.
IT HAD UNLIMITED ACCESS
TO MY CREDIT CARD
IN A TOY STORE.
WE GOT LIKE FIVE
KIDS, FIVE.
AND IT WON'T EVER.
THE STRAY KIDS SURPRISED
EZRA WITH A MEATY
GROUP AND EVEN WASHED
THEM HER FORM LIVE.
BROOKE GOT TO COOK
ALONGSIDE CHRISTINA TOZI IN
AWARD -WINNING CHEF. THIS
IS GORGEOUS.
AND EVEN CREATE HER
OWN DESSERT ON THE
MENU.
AND THIS IS AMAZING.
SHELBY EXPLORED A HAUNTED
MUSEUM IN VEGAS WITH
SAM AND COLBY.
COLBY HAD CANCER, SO
I FEEL LIKE I
CAN RELATE TO HIM.
I REALLY DO LIKE
THEM. AND JOSHUA GOT
THE LASER ENGRAVER HE'D
BEEN DREAMING OF. THIS
IS BETTER THAN HE
THOUGHT I COULD HAVE
IMAGINED. AND ALIA. THAT'S
FOR APPLE PRODUCTS. WHAT'S
SURPRISING.
I HEARD YOU WANTED
SOME APPLE PRODUCTS. THANK
YOU. FOR OUR NEXT
FEW WISHES, WE BROUGHT
MR. BEAST VIDEOS TO
THEM. HAVE ANY OF
YOU EVER WANTED TO
COMPETE IN A MINI
-MR. BEAST VIDEO? YES!
OKAY. WE'VE GOT MINI
VERSIONS OF OUR VIDEOS
SET UP ALL AROUND
THIS ROOM. ONE MORE
FOR IT. LET'S GO!
YOU DID IT!
OH!
LET'S SEE IF WE
CAN CATCH THE WIND
AND SAIL TO THE
ISLAND! YOU GET A
BRAND NEW XBOX AS
A GIFT FROM US.
HERE YOU GO. IT'S
LITTLE HEAVY. CONGRATULATIONS!
AND FOR OUR NEXT
WISH, WE PARTNERED WITH
DISNEY TO FLY THREE
KIDS TO HAWAII FOR
AN UNFORGETTABLE WEEK AT
DISNEY'S OWN LONNIE RESORT.
ALOHA! AND WELCOME TO
HAWAII! YOU TO SAY
YOU SHOULD HIT IT?
I GOT IT. ALOHA,
AND WELCOME TO HAWAII.
ARE YOU READY TO
ROCK THE BEST MAKING
YOUR ENTIRE LIFE? YEAH!
AND AFTER MEETING MICKEY
AND HIS FRIENDS. THANK
YOU!
AND TAKING A DIP
IN THE TROPICAL OCEAN.
ARE YOU OKAY?
I'LL GO BACK TO
THE SHORE. WE BROUGHT
THEM ON A HELICOPTER
TOUR AROUND THE ENTIRE
ISLAND.